
var questions = [{
	"question": "1The switch is switched off once the temperature falls below 18 and then it is turned on when the temperature is more than 21. Identify the equivalence values which belong to the same class?",
	"option1": "14, 15, 17",
	"option2": "24, 17, 17",
	"option3": "22, 23, 24",
	"option4": "12, 16, 22",
	"answer":  "3",
	"website":    "https://www.softwaretestinghelp.com"

},{
	"question":"2In a system designed to work out the tax to be paid: An employee has $4000 of salary tax free. The next $1500 is taxed at 10%, the next $28000 is taxed at 22%, any further amount is taxed at 40%. Which of these groups of number would fall into the same equivalence class?",
	"option1": "$5800, $28000, $2000",
	"option2": "$28000, $32000, $35000",
	"option3": "$4800, $14000, $28000",
	"option4": "$5200, $5500, $28000",
	"answer":  "1",
	"website":    "https://reqtest.com"

},{

	"question":"3A software Engineering student would like to do a thorough testing on every compound of my new application, in order to avoid the chances of bugs after the application is released to the market. Which of the testing do you think is the for the application?",
	"option1": "Unit Testing",
	"option2": "Gorilla Testing",
	"option3": "Functional Testing",
	"option4": "Monkey Testing",
	"answer":  "2",
	"website":    "https://www.tutorialspoint.com"

},{

	"question":"4An Engineer was informed that his application may encounter defects in later stages where it can't be cost effective if I don't a testing. Which of this testing do I need to perform in early stages to identify the defects?",
	"option1": "Sanity Testing",
	"option2": "Statement Testing",
	"option3": "Smoke Testing",
	"option4": "Path Testing",
	"answer":  "3",
	"website":    "https://www.softwaretestingclass.com"

},{
	"question":"5A testing designed to touch every part of the application, which testing is broad, shallow and suitable enough for this kind of suitable",
	"option1": "Smoke Testing",
	"option2": "Statement Testing",
	"option3": "Sanity Testing",
	"option4": "Path Testing",
	"answer":  "1",
	"website":    "https://www.careerride.com"
},{
	"question": "6To verify whether requirement elicitation for the system are met, Which testing is deep and narrow, that focuses on one or few areas of functionality?",
	"option1": "Smoke Testing",
	"option2": "Statement Testing",
	"option3": "Sanity Testing",
	"option4": "Path Testing",
	"answer":  "3",
	"website":    "https://www.careerride.com"
},{
	"question":"7Which of the following is not a white box testing technique",
	"option1": "Statement Testing",
	"option2": "Data flow Testing",
	"option3": "Path Testing",
	"option4": "State Transition Testing",
	"answer":  "4",
	"website":    "https://www.tutorialspoint.com"
},{

	"question": "8Which of the following could be a reason for failure? 1) Testing fault 2) software fault 3) Design fault 4) Environmental fault 5) Documentation fault",
	"option1": "2 is a valid reason",
	"option2": "1234 are valid reasons; 5 is not",
	"option3": "All of the above are valid reasons for failure",
	"option4": "23 are valid reasons; 145 are not",
	"answer": "3",
	"website":    ""
},{

	"question": "9Test are priotized so that we",
	"option1": "Do more effective Testing",
	"option2": "Shorten the time required for Testing",
	"option3": "Do the best Testing in the time available",
	"option4": "Find more faults",
	"answer": "3",
	"website":    ""
},{
	"question":"10The purpose of requirement phase",
	"option1": "To define the scope of testing",
	"option2": "To freeze requirement",
	"option3": "To understand the user needs",
	"option4": "All of the above",
	"answer":"4",
	"website":    "https://searchsoftwarequality.com"
},{
	"question": "11What is the difference between testing software developed by contractor outside your country versus software testing developed by contractor within your country?",
	"option1": "cultural difference",
	"option2": "Does not meet peoples need",
	"option3": "Relinquishment of control",
	"option4": "loss of control over reallocation of resources",
	"answer":  "1",
	"website":    ""
},{
	"question":"12Data collected during testing should include",
	"option1":"Test factor",
	"option2":"Functions/subroutines",
	"option3":"Non of the above",
	"option4":"All of the above",
	"answer": "4",
	"website":    ""
},{

	"question": "13When a new testing tool is purchased, it should be used first by?",
	"option1": "A small tean to establish the best way to use the tool",
	"option2": "The independent testing team",
	"option3": "Everyone who may eventually have some use for the tool",
	"option4": "The vendor contractor to write to write the initial script",
	"answer": "1",
	"website":    ""
},{

	"question": "14Software verification is?",
	"option1": "Checking that we are building the right system",
	"option2": "Performed by an independent test team",
	"option3": "Make sure it is what the user really want",
	"option4": "Checking that we are building the right system",
	"answer": "4",
	"website":  "http://tryqa.com"
},{
	"question":"15A realiable website/application will be the one which",
	"option1": "is unlikely to be completed on schedule",
	"option2": "is unlikely to cause a failure",
	"option3": "is likely to be fault free",
	"option4": "is likely to be liked by the users",
	"answer": "2",
	"website":    ""
}];
